Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/upekshasandamini (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Quality Assurance

Project Management

Payment Application Data Security Standards

Languages

English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Navigating Complexities of Software Licence Agreements

Deeply Practical Project Management (16 PDUs)

Business Analysis Fundamentals Identify & Define the Problem with Business Analysis

Upeksha Sandamini

Associate Software Quality Assurance Lead at Calcey Technologies Kalutara District, Western Province, Sri Lanka

Summary

I am an Associate QA Lead Engineer and a Scrum Master with over 5 years of experience in several business domains including Banking and Finance, AFC, e-Wallets etc..

As a QA engineer, I have involved in the full software development life cycle from design to implementation and held many responsibilities including team leadership, requirement analysis, planning and effort estimation, software security assurance, Test Plan preparation, test execution, project documentation etc. Good communication skills developed by working with diverse teams - both local and foreign, and the professional client handling skills have added me more value as a QA engineer and a Project Coordinator.

Experience

Calcey

Associate Software Quality Assurance Lead February 2022 - Present (1 year 8 months)

DH3 Solutions Private Limited

2 years 4 months

Senior Software Quality Assurance Engineer May 2021 - February 2022 (10 months)

Performed a multifaceted role as a Senior QA Engineer and a Project Manager

Software Quality Assurance Engineer November 2019 - May 2021 (1 year 7 months)

Silverleap Technology Private Limited 2 years 3 months

Quality Assurance Engineer August 2019 - November 2019 (4 months)

43, Dehiwala rd, Pepiliyana

Associate Software Quality Assurance Engineer April 2018 - July 2019 (1 year 4 months)

43, Dehiwala rd, Pepiliyana

Intern Quality Assurance Engineer September 2017 - March 2018 (7 months)

Completed six months of internship as a QA Engineer

AIESEC in University of Sri Jayewardenepura 1 year 8 months

Project Team Lead November 2016 - December 2017 (1 year 2 months) University of Sri Jayewardenepura

Organizing Committee Vise President
May 2016 - December 2017 (1 year 8 months)
Worked as the OCVP - Logistics of Gurugedara 6.0

Society of Computer Science - University of Sri Jayewardenepura Assistant Secretary January 2016 - February 2017 (1 year 2 months) University of Sri Jayewardenepura

Education

University of Sri Jayewardenepura
Bachelor's degree, Physical Sciences · (2015 - 2018)

Panadura Balika Maha Vidyalaya Combined Mathematics · (2006 - 2013)